

## Profile

Work experience for almost 10 years. My direct specialty is web developer. However, if necessary, I can easily learn any programming language. I work on php / mysql, confidently familiar with the jquery and css. I have experience with such CMS as: 1C-Bitrix, Joomla, WordPress, Drupal

## Education

**Second degree, Ulyanovsk State Technical University, Ulyanovsk** September 2009 — June 2014

# Employment History

Programmer at Ulyanovsk State Technical University, Ulyanovsk, Ulyanovsk

September 2010 — August 2012

Was engaged in the development / maintenance of the "Educational Process" system. PHP development. Work with databases, MySQL, PostgreSQL

# Web-developer at Digital Dream LLC, Ulyanovsk

August 2012 — August 2013

Website development on the 1C-Bitrix platform. During his work in the company, 17 projects were successfully completed, sites of medium complexity and higher.

## Web-developer at Individual entrepreneur, Ulyanovsk

August 2012 — July 2014

During freelance, at least two dozens of sites were developed from corporate web applications to highly loaded online stores.

#### Web-developer at IntimeFinance, Ulyanovsk

April 2014 — October 2015

Web application development for the internal needs of the company, corporate site development. System administration.

### Web-developer, Teamleader at iBrush, Moscow

October 2015 — December 2018

Website development, management of a development team (3 programmers, 2 layout designers), design, maintenance. Interview new staff.

# Web-developer, Teamlead at Eapteka Ltd, Moscow

January 2019 — Present

Work on a highly loaded project - daily the number of visitors is several hundred thousand.

#### **Details**

Netanya, Israel, +972 50-584-8836 paulberg73@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 16/03/1992 Russia

Nationality Israeli, Russia

#### **Skills**

php

Css

MySql

jQuery

**AJAX** 

Git

Git Flow

Seo

HTML5

Docker

**Effective Team Leader** 

Ability to Work in a Team

## Languages

English

Russian